export const data = [
    {
        question: "What is the full form of HTML?",
        option1: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        option2: "Hyper Tough Markup Language",
        option3: "Heat Type Markup Language",
        option4: "Hyper Text Markeup Land",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the use of HTML?",
        option1: "For AI",
        option2: "For animation",
        option3: "To create Machine",
        option4: "To create layout of webpage",
        ans: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Current Version of HTMl?",
        option1: "HTML",
        option2: "HTML3",
        option3: "HTML5",
        option4: "HTML4",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the use of <p></p> tag?",
        option1: "To create polinomium",
        option2: "Making Paragraph in webpage",
        option3: "Creating pattern",
        option4: "for pagination",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the use of div?",
        option1: "to create seperate area",
        option2: "to create form input",
        option3: "to create pagination",
        option4: "Making diver Type",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Use of <b> tag in HTML.",
        option1: "for text underline",
        option2: "for bolding the text",
        option3: "for text distance",
        option4: "none of these",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the use of semantic tags?",
        option1: "For styling",
        option2: "To create layout of website",
        option3: "Semantic tags used for SEO",
        option4: "none of these",
        ans: 3,
    },
]

// css 

export const cssData = [
    {
        question: "What is the full form of CSS?",
        option1: "Cascading Stylesheet",
        option2: "Component Short Selection",
        option3: "Common Seperate Style",
        option4: "Command Selular Screen",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "How to select ID's in HTML?",
        option1: "using .",
        option2: "using #",
        option3: "using *",
        option4: "none of these",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Why we use media query?",
        option1: "For animation",
        option2: "for color effect",
        option3: "for responsive web design",
        option4: "none of these",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the use of <p></p> tag?",
        option1: "To create polinomium",
        option2: "Making Paragraph on web page",
        option3: "Creating path",
        option4: "none of these",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the use of CSS?",
        option1: "Designing the web page",
        option2: "making functions",
        option3: "creating programs for ML",
        option4: "none",
        ans: 1,
    },
] 


export const jsData = [
    {
        question: "What is the full form of JS?",
        option1: "Javascript",
        option2: "Java Searching",
        option3: "Jarvis",
        option4: "Java Server",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Javascript is a ... language?",
        option1: "compiling",
        option2: "scripting",
        option3: "a and b both",
        option4: "none of these",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "How to create variable in js?",
        option1: "using string and int",
        option2: "there is no need of variable",
        option3: "using let, var, and const",
        option4: "none of these",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "What is the current version of javacript?",
        option1: "1.2",
        option2: "ES6",
        option3: "BS6",
        option4: "none of these",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "How to use js in html?",
        option1: "Using script tag",
        option2: "cloud",
        option3: "using ML",
        option4: "none",
        ans: 1,
    },
] 